Thank you for watching!
I'll do my best!
Wow!
It's done!
Can-can-can!
Ladies and gentlemen!
Good evening.
I'm Hitoko.
Last week...
I've been introducing our camping gear.
I'd like to introduce our camping gear.
This time
Well, here it is!
Last week, I introduced
I introduced last week.
I'd like to use it
I'd like to do some battling.
Or rather, I would like to do battling.
I've never battled before.
I've never battled before, so it's a bit like a practice video.
I've never battled before, so it's kind of like a practice video.
This tree...
This is...
It's a small one.
The first thing to do is to make a fire.
The smaller and thinner the wood is, the easier it is to start a fire.
It's easier to start a fire.
Yes, sir.
So I would like to do this one.
If you can do it, it's so cool!
It's so cool!
One channel
Yes
So I'm going to use this one.
I'm going to do it using this one.
I say I'll do it.
I've never done it before.
Practice.
I'll start with practice.
I'll do my best.
Hey, everyone!
Please cheer for me in front of the screen.
Oh, here.
Experienced campers?
Please leave your tips and tricks in the comment section!
I'd love to hear from you.
You know what?
I found a bug on the tree.
I think it's gonna be okay.
I'll do my best.
Good night. - Good night.
All right. - All right.
I'll open it.
Your face is all cut up.
I'm not gonna lie.
It's heavy.
Is that right?
A little slanted.
Oh!
There's a bug.
Keep it up.
You're a go-getter, aren't you?
You're taking this one.
I'll make it even smaller
Here we go.
Oh, wow
Ha, ha.
That's good. That's good. That's pretty good.
It's done!
Take a break.
I hope the wind doesn't blow it away.
The sound is wonderful.
Look at that.
It's done.
You may be more talented than you think.
But, you know, after this.
What was that? Feather stick?
No?
You know, you rip them up, like so...
And then we make the real thing.We're going to make a real one.
That sounds more fun.
Let's do it.
Let's do it! Yeah! - Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah! Let's go for it!
I think I've got it.
I'll have to make a few thin ones.
Let's try a few.
This is also my first time doing this.
So forgive me if I can't do it.
What?
Oh!
It's difficult.
The future
I can't see it.
I can't.
What? Look at this.
What? Is it big? I don't know if I'm...
I don't think so.
You're good!
But it's definitely not like this.
Thank you for watching.
Oh, look at me!
Just in case you wanted to go.
Mazbovs.
I'm here to collect.
Lady.
Right here, right there.
Three, two.
Thank you for watching.
Can we talk about the little tree?
sort of.
And I'm not at all done with this my
I've got a full stick.
I'm going to light it on fire.
Here's a little
Fire.
I don't know if I'm doing it right.
I don't know if spockles catch fire.
See you later.
But it's making a crackling sound.
It's hot!
That's good, right?
I think it's on, don't you?
It's burning like a summer candle.
Here we go.
Okay, everybody.
I think we're here.
Unless a strong wind blew it away, it's probably here.
I'm so happy.
Yay!
It's windy, too.
Feels good
Oh, it's so warm
It's finally warm.
Ooh!
That's nice.
Reflections on this time
Soraiichi
I couldn't make feather sticks at all!
I'm going to study that one a little bit by watching a video.
Completion point 2
I should have chosen a day when the wind was a little weaker.
Wait a minute!
This is not good.
I'm gonna put a big one in there.
I'm gonna burn it.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
But I'm glad we got here.
Thank you all for watching what may have been a long video!
See you next week!
Bye-bye!
(Ending)
Thank you for watching!